Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Gracie Mansion Gallery records
- Business Records, 1982-1991, Series 3:; (Box 5, 1 linear foot)
  - Artist (Box 5)
    - Claudia DeMonte: Fine Arts Resources Presentation, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Claudia DeMonte: Jennifer Muller Art Sale, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Claudia DeMonte: Marcia Yerman Request, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Rodney Alan Greenblat: Nunotani Company of America, Inc., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Mike Howard: 225 Fifth Avenue Commission, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Lack: Modern Art Consultants, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gary Panter: Majima Design Calendar, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hope Sandrow: Dakis Joannou Commission, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Auction (Box 5)
    - "A Bid of Love" AIDS Auction, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Artists' Lofts Benefit Auction, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Contemporary Art Auction, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Houston Auction, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Joe Mittleman Auction, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - National Abortion Rights Action League Benefit Auction, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - New Museum Benefit Auction, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Save the Children's Programs Silent Auction, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Barneys New York, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Art Unlimited, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Galerie Barbara Ferber, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Karl Bornstein Gallery, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Fine Art Packers, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Viart Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Walls Art and Design, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Prentice Hall, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - E.B. Harrington and Company, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Gracie Mansion Museum Store, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Graphics, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Lists (Box 5)
    - Artist Lectures (1985-1989), circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Catalogs and Publications (1982-1990), circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - International Press and Publications (1982-1989), circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Selected Group Exhibitions (1985-1990), circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Logos, circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Michael C. Burrows Letter, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - New, Used and Improved: Art in the '80's Book, circa 1980s (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Portfolio Lithography, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Possible Shows, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Returned Consignment Forms (Box 5)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 41-42)
    - 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Trapp Associates, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Unknown Photograph, circa 1980s (Box 5, Folder 45)